<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Japan Travel</string>
    <string name="fact_1">Japan is made up of over 6,800 islands, with Honshu being the largest and most populous of them all.</string>
    <string name="fact_2">Mount Fuji, Japan’s tallest mountain at 3,776 meters, is an iconic symbol and a popular climbing destination.</string>
    <string name="fact_3">Japan has one of the world’s highest life expectancies, with an average of over 84 years for both genders.</string>
    <string name="fact_4">Tokyo, Japan’s capital, is the most populous metropolitan area in the world, home to over 37 million people.</string>
    <string name="fact_5">Japan experiences around 1,500 earthquakes annually due to its location on the Pacific Ring of Fire tectonic zone.</string>
    <string name="fact_6">Shinkansen, or bullet trains, can reach speeds of up to 320 km/h and are famous for their punctuality and safety.</string>
    <string name="fact_7">Sumo wrestling is Japan’s national sport, rooted in ancient Shinto rituals and performed in large clay rings called dohyō.</string>
    <string name="fact_8">Japan has more vending machines per capita than any other country, selling everything from drinks to umbrellas and hot meals.</string>
    <string name="fact_9">The Japanese writing system combines three scripts: Kanji, Hiragana, and Katakana, each used for different linguistic functions.</string>
    <string name="fact_10">Cherry blossom season, or Sakura, is a major cultural event celebrated with picnics and festivals throughout Japan in spring.</string>
    <string name="fact_11">Japan is home to 25 UNESCO World Heritage Sites, including historic temples, shrines, castles, and natural wonders like Yakushima Island.</string>
    <string name="fact_12">Japanese cuisine emphasizes seasonality and presentation, with sushi, ramen, tempura, and wagyu beef known around the world.</string>
    <string name="fact_13">Japan has a strong tradition of craftsmanship, producing high-quality goods such as ceramics, swords, textiles, and electronics.</string>
    <string name="fact_14">The country’s population is rapidly aging, with nearly 30% of Japanese people over the age of 65 as of recent years.</string>
    <string name="fact_15">Kyoto, the ancient capital, is known for its well-preserved temples, gardens, geisha culture, and traditional wooden architecture.</string>
    <string name="fact_16">Japanese schoolchildren clean their classrooms and facilities themselves, as part of teaching responsibility and community values.</string>
    <string name="fact_17">Japan’s culture blends ancient traditions with modern innovation, from tea ceremonies and kabuki theater to robotics and anime.</string>
    <string name="title_1">Japan’s Islands</string>
    <string name="title_2">Mount Fuji</string>
    <string name="title_3">Life Expectancy</string>
    <string name="title_4">Tokyo Population</string>
    <string name="title_5">Earthquake Activity</string>
    <string name="title_6">Bullet Trains</string>
    <string name="title_7">Sumo Wrestling</string>
    <string name="title_8">Vending Machines</string>
    <string name="title_9">Writing System</string>
    <string name="title_10">Cherry Blossom Season</string>
    <string name="title_11">World Heritage Sites</string>
    <string name="title_12">Japanese Cuisine</string>
    <string name="title_13">Craftsmanship</string>
    <string name="title_14">Aging Population</string>
    <string name="title_15">Kyoto’s Heritage</string>
    <string name="title_16">School Cleaning Culture</string>
    <string name="title_17">Tradition and Innovation</string>
    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
</resources>